greenhitz.com 2009-06-17

# GreenHitz.com - A Record Breaking Community - Privacy Policy

  * **GreenHitz.com Privacy Policy**   
GreenHitz.com’s privacy policy covers the collection and use of personal information that may be collected by GreenHitz.com anytime you interact with GreenHitz.com, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase GreenHitz.com products and services, or when you call our sales or support associates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at GreenHitz.com, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

  * **GreenHitz.com (Label Edition) Privacy**  
GreenHitz.com does not utilize, rent or sell any email addresses or other contact information that you provide or collect regarding your email list members. At all times, you retain ownership and control of your email lists and list information. Please keep your account username(s) and password(s) secure at all times, changing your password regularly as you would on other computer systems to prevent unauthorized access or use. In order to comply with government legislation, email addresses which have requested no further contact will be placed on a suppression list which may be accessed by other organizations to maintain suppression of such addresses in their mailings as well as ours.

  * **GreenHitz.com Collects Personal Information**   
GreenHitz.com collects personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about. If you do not want GreenHitz.com to keep you up to date with GreenHitz.com news, updates and the latest information on products and services follow the unsubscribe list located at the bottom of the email.   

  * **The Information GreenHitz.com Collects**   
There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better service. For example, we may ask for your personal information when you’re discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, downloading a software update, registering for a seminar, participating in an online survey, registering your products, or purchasing a product. At such times, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the GreenHitz.com products you own, such as their serial numbers, and date of purchase; and information relating to a support or service issue. We collect information for market research purposes — such as your occupation and where you use your computer — to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service. We also collect information regarding customer activities on our website, the GreenHitz.com Service, the GreenHitz.com Record Pool, and on related websites. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites and Internet services are of most interest to them. The GreenHitz.com website, as well as GreenHitz.com services such as the GreenHitz.com Service, the GreenHitz.com Record Pool and our related services, allows you to create an “GreenHitz.com ID” based on your personal information. This convenient service saves you time and allows for easier use of our web services. Here’s how it works: You create a personal profile — providing your name, phone number, email address, and in some cases your mailing address or a credit card number — and choose a password and password hint (such as the month and day of your birth) for security. The system saves your information and assigns you a personal GreenHitz.com ID — in many cases simply your email address, because it’s unique and easy to remember. The next time you order from the GreenHitz.com Store or register a new product, all you need to do is enter your GreenHitz.com ID and password; the system looks up the information it needs to assist you. In addition, if you update the information associated with your GreenHitz.com ID it will be available for all your transactions with GreenHitz.com globally.   
If you use a bulletin board or chat room on an GreenHitz.com website you should be aware that any information you share is visible to other users. Personally identifiable information you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected, or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages. GreenHitz.com is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.  

  * **GreenHitz.com Disclosure of Information**   
GreenHitz.com takes your privacy very seriously. Be assured that GreenHitz.com does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers. To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within the GreenHitz.com group globally who will safeguard it in accordance with GreenHitz.com’s privacy policy. There are also times when it may be advantageous for GreenHitz.com to make certain personal information about you available to companies that GreenHitz.com has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for GreenHitz.com to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with GreenHitz.com’s policies. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and content on the GreenHitz.com website. At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.   

  * **GreenHitz.com Protects Your Personal Information**   
GreenHitz.com takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. We utilize secure servers, and do our best to protect any information we collect over the internet. You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Safari.   

  * **Integrity of your personal information**   
GreenHitz.com has safeguards in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. Naturally, you always have the right to access and correct the personal information you have provided. You can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by checking at www.GreenHitz.com.com And you can request a copy of your personal information, your download history, and your interactions with our sales and support agents by contacting us at the email address below.   

  * **Cookies and other technologies**   
As is standard practice on many corporate websites, GreenHitz.com’s website uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We also use cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our products and services. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.   
Information such as your country and language — and if you’re an disc jockey, your station call letters — helps us provide a more useful online experience. And your contact information and information about your computer helps us register your products, personalize your experience, and set up your Internet Service and accounts and provide you with customer service.   
As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. GreenHitz.com will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.   
In some of our email messages we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the GreenHitz.com website. When a customer clicks one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email. In addition we use pixel tags — tiny graphic images — to tell us what parts of our website customers have visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches customers perform on our site. Pixel tags also enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read. And they tell us whether emails have been opened to assure that we’re only sending messages that are of interest to our customers. We store all of this information in a secure database located in Atlanta, Georgia in the United States.   

  * **GreenHitz.com is committed to your privacy**   
As we said, GreenHitz.com takes protecting your privacy very seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to GreenHitz.com employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company. In addition, GreenHitz.com supports industry initiatives — such as the Online Privacy Alliance and TRUSTe — to preserve privacy rights on the Internet and in all aspects of electronic commerce. And we do not knowingly solicit personal information from minors or send them requests for personal information. GreenHitz.com abides by the safe harbor framework set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information collected from the European Union. You’ll find more information about the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program.   
GreenHitz.com’s website has links to the sites of other companies. GreenHitz.com is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.   

  * **Privacy questions**   
If you have questions or concerns about GreenHitz.com’s Customer Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us at GreenHitz@GreenHitz.com   
GreenHitz.com may update its privacy policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated privacy policy.
